[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
=Remnants of Gold=
(Adapted from Gu Long's
"Flying Eagle over the Great Land")
(The main characters
in this drama are fictional)
=Episode 13=
The water isn't deep.
You can cross.
I said you can cross.
They can't speak.
My name is Tang Zheng.
Why can't they speak?
Their tongues were cut out.
They agreed to it.
My name is Tang Zheng.
I know.
What's your name?
Bancha.
Does this water
have a name?
Nether Sea.
I've never seen the sea.
But I know
the sea doesn't look like this.
Then what should it look like?
In the northern depths
lives a fish called Kun.
Kun is so vast, and no one knows how
many hundreds of kilometers it spans.
It transforms into a bird called Peng.
Peng's back
spans countless hundreds of kilometers.
When it takes flight,
its wings are like
clouds hanging from the sky.
Look at the state you're in,
and you still love to talk.
The sea should be vast.
The Nether Sea is only this big.
We also call it Nether Water.
It's not deep.
You can cross.
I can't cross water.
I never cross water.
I've come all the way
from Northern Sichuan
without crossing water once.
You came
all the way
from Northern Sichuan like this?
Once you cross the Nether Water,
what's beyond
those sand dunes?
Wusu Sea.
Is there a real sea there?
There's no sea.
It's just called Wusu Sea.
That's no fun.
Hurry.
Faster.
Do you have to
cross the Nether Water
to reach Wusu Sea?
Was Zhang Luyao happy
after coming to the Northwest?
What did you say?
For days,
I've been following you.
I never thought she'd die.
The Zhang lady is dead?
She died in Ganzhou.
They're bringing her this way now,
to Wusu Sea.
Why?
One night,
she told someone
that when she died,
she wanted to be buried at Wusu Sea.
Who are you to her?
Five years ago,
she came to the Tang Clan
to marry me.
So you're waiting here for her.
You're taking her back to the Tang Clan?
No.
I'm going to cremate her.
The dead deserve respect.
They should be laid to rest.
I used many medicines on her.
I'll cremate her,
and then slowly consume her ashes.
They may have some medicinal effect.
But she was your woman.
She never married me.
She's a human being, too!
I'm crippled. You noticed, didn't you?
Zhang Luyao used to be the same.
I used many poisons on her,
hoping to cure myself through her.
But unexpectedly,
she recovered,
while I remained like this.
Was she happy before she died?
Her entire family was slaughtered,
and then she met someone like you.
How could she be happy?
You don't understand someone like me.
Whenever others are happy,
I suffer.
How badly?
Bancha.
Are you happy?
I've been miserable these past few days.
Right now, I'm extremely unhappy.
Then, leave.
Go.
What do you mean?
You can go now.
It's this bell that's moving.
She isn't moving?
It's scorching hot inside the carriage,
but she's cold as ice.
Would you like
to see for yourself, Officer?
No.
Why are you still
going to Wusu Sea, Officer?
Everyone searching
for the gold is already dead.
I'm not looking for the gold.
Zhang Luyao wanted
to be buried at Wusu Sea.
You're going there just to bury her?
Yes.
But I want to return to Liangzhou.
Once we bury her
at Wusu Sea, you can leave.
I can't bring myself to do it.
You're a coroner.
Was that man just now human
or some kind of monster?
Bancha, are you scared?
What are you doing?
Keep heading north.
When you see the first yurt,
tell them you're Bana's son.
What are you doing?
Go!
When are you returning
to the Capital, Officer?
Do you want to know?
No.
Not at all.
How much longer to Wusu Sea?
Once we cross the Nether Sea ahead,
we'll make it before dark if we hurry.
Nether Sea?
(Wusu Sea)
You're Tang Zheng, right?
You asked me earlier if I was happy.
Ask me again.
Bancha.
Are you happy?
Very happy.
Really?
I never lie.
That's why I came back
just to tell you again.
I've always been happy.
Especially today.
Right now, I'm extremely happy.
I envy you so much.
Don't envy me.
I want to see you suffer.
You came back
just to give me a reason to kill you.
You make the first move.
Then I'll have a reason to kill you.
For Zhang Luyao?
Enough talk.
Your voice is awful.
Each rib of my fan
has a different poison on it.
Even I don't know
what will happen to you.
Bancha.
Are you still happy?
Very happy.
So happy I could fly.
That's the poison taking effect.
How many fingers are on your right hand?
Take a look.
Have they turned into five earthworms?
Sometimes
they merge into one.
Other times,
cherries start growing from your mouth.
You watch them grow taller and taller.
Your eyes turn into two fish
and sink into the water.
Isn't that right?
Poison affects everyone differently.
Zhang Luyao came back
from the brink of death many times,
but she still died in the end.
You'll be dead soon, too.
Do you see it?
He looks like a ghost.
So ugly.
Even I'm scared.
Then don't look if you're scared.
Pretend you didn't see anything.
Stop looking.
Let's go over there.
The water here isn't good.
Isn't it?
It must be freezing.
What if it splashes on you?
Why bother?
I already let you go.
Even if you do this,
Zhang Luyao will never know.
My men
will be here soon.
And then?
They'll take Zhang Luyao
to Wusu Sea.
Why bother?
My friend
wants to go to Wusu Sea...
You know Zhang Luyao?
You know her, too?
Not really.
We were hoping
to follow her to find some gold.
Are you happy?
What do you mean?
Are you
happy?
Of course.
Every day with Yan makes me happy.
You've looked miserable the whole way,
and you still call that happy?
He's asking if I'm happy inside.
He must be invisible.
Is he even human?
And that voice is awful.
What does it sound like?
A crow!
A crow with no wings,
cawing desperately!
Right?
Yan.
You can never watch your mouth.
And how am I supposed to do that?
You'll upset the crow.
Yan!
Yan.
It's fine.
You're wearing Tie Futu's
Soft Hedgehog Armor.
Let's go
back to Northern Shu...
Look.
So many cherry trees have grown tall.
So many cherries.
They're all yellow,
one by one,
like gold.
Yes.
Trying to leave? Where can you go?
Do you see them?
So many
golden cherries.
I see them, Yan.
They're all golden.
All of them.
Golden cherry trees.
Bancha.
Bancha is dead.
They killed Bancha.
You don't know martial arts?
No.
I didn't injure this man.
If not you, then who?
This is infuriating.
Yan's wound is the same as his!
Who are you?
Nobody.
What are you doing here?
Do you have a death wish?
You...
We meant to return to Mount Pingfeng,
but took the wrong road.
This is the Nether Sea?
Yes.
This is the Nether Sea.
There's not much water left.
The sea is much bigger than this.
How big?
Very big.
This is just a ditch.
Officer Pu said a ditch is a ditch.
Cross this ditch
and go over that sand dune.
Wusu Sea is just beyond it.
Is it a real sea?
I've never been there.
Let's go.
Officer Pu.
Listen.
Don't move.
Do you have any water?
We're standing in water.
I'm very thirsty.
Give me some.
I knew it.
It's like a dream.
Officer Pu.
I'll get you some water.
Where are we going?
Wusu Sea.
We're almost there.
Here.
That's nice.
He's not coming with us?
He wants to return to Liangzhou.
Sit tight.
Let's get down.
Thank you.
Sit tight.
=Remnants of Gold=